<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source>
  <publisher>GigSafe</publisher>
  <publisherurl>https://www.gigsafe.com/</publisherurl>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Delivery Driver]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2025-12-18 23:25:34]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[11]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://gigsafe-jobboard.replit.app/jobs/11]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[RedWagon Delivers]]></company>
    <address><![CDATA[]]></address>
    <city><![CDATA[Mountain View]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[CA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <postalcode><![CDATA[94041]]></postalcode>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>"The RedWagon Delivers is seeking reliable, motivated independent contractors to join our delivery team. Our ideal candidate has experience with platforms such as DoorDash, Grubhub, or Uber Eats, and understands how partnering with RedWagon can increase overall earnings. As a 1099 contractor, you will manage your own schedule and operate as an independent business partner.</p><p><br></p><p>Deliveries typically take 30 minutes and are most frequent between 9 AM and 2 PM, though routes are available from 6 AM to 9 PM, seven days a week. Your availability directly determines your earning potential. Compensation is per delivery, not hourly. Top earners regularly make between $50 and $200+ per day.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Qualifications:</strong> </p><p>- Minimum age of 21</p><p>- Valid U.S. driver’s license</p><p>- Smartphone with navigation capability</p><p>- Reliable personal vehicle (van or truck not required)</p><p>- Strong communication and problem-solving skills</p><p>- Excellent attention to detail and ability to follow directions</p><p>- If onboarded, you must provide your own delivery equipment, including catering bags (23x13x15) and a collapsible cart, wagon, or hand truck. These items are required to meet client standards.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p><p>- Pick up and deliver food or other items promptly and professionally</p><p>- Transport orders safely and maintain quality during delivery</p><p>- Set up orders at customer locations when requested (light setup only)</p><p>- Accept deliveries across a range of pay levels</p><p>- Represent The RedWagon Delivers with professionalism in appearance and attitude</p><p>- Maintain exceptional customer service standards on every delivery</p><p>- Work schedule</p><p>- Monday to Friday</p><p>- Weekend availability</p><p>- Supplemental pay</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Pt. Time/Contract]]></jobtype>
    <category><![CDATA[Logistics]]></category>
    <notification><![CDATA[jimmy@gigsafe.com]]></notification>
  </job>
</source>